http://www.liberator.com/privacy-policy.html

25%
OFF SITEWIDE*
code:
OFF SITEWIDE*
code:
HOLIDAY
| view offers
Liberator Collection Original Label ShapesBlack Label ShapesSex Pillows & ThrowsSex Toy MountsCovers & GearbagsCuffs & AccessoriesConversion Kits
Check it out
BOTTOM'S UP!
Heartfelt Coasters
Sex FurnitureSex Chaises & Sex LoungersBlack Label Sex ChaisesSex Furniture Conversion KitsSex Furniture 101
Use Sezzle
BondageLeather Cuffs & CollarsMasks & BlindfoldsSpanking ToolsBondage GearSensation PlayTemperature PlayBody HarnessesKinky Toys
FREE COCK RING
w/ any CalExotics purchase!
MASQUERADE
Role Play
Sex ToysLuxury VibratorsApp Controlled Sex ToysClitoral StimulatorsVibratorsRabbit VibratorsG-Spot VibratorsElectro Sex ToysWands & MassagersBullet VibratorsDildosMetal ToysGlass ToysAnal ToysMen's ToysCouple's ToysToy MountsToy HarnessesToy Cases & AccessoriesKegel Balls
Dildos
Vibrators
Luxury Vibrators
Clitoral Stimulators
Rabbit Vibrators
G-Spot Vibrators
Wands & Massagers
Bullet Vibrators
FREE JELLY COCK RING
w/ any Oxballs purchase!
Body & GiftsWater-based LubesSilicone LubesNatural LubesEdible TreatsToy & Personal CareMassage Oils & CandlesOils & StimulantsLove is ArtGifts For HerGifts For HimGifts For UsGifts Under $300Gifts Under $150Gifts Under $75Gift CardsFace Masks
Water-Based Lubes
Silicone Lubes
Natural Lubes
Edible Treats
Toy & Personal Care
Massage Oils & Candles
Arousal Oils & Stimulants
Love Is Art
FREE TOTE BAG
w/ Any Womanizer purchase!
BOTTOM'S UP!
Heartfelt Coasters
Brands We LoveAnerosBathmateb-VibeCalExoticsElectroShockFun FactoryJimmyJaneKIIROOLELOMagic WandnjoyOxballsTantusWe-VibeWomanizer
Aneros
b-Vibe
Bathmate
CalExotics
ElectroShock
Fun Factory
KIIROO
LELO
FREE VIBRATING C-RING
w/ any CalExotics purchase!
Best SellersLiberator Best SellersBondage Best SellersSex Toys Best SellersBody & Gifts Best Sellers
Liberator Best Sellers
Bondage Best Sellers
Sex Toys Best Sellers
Body & Gifts Best Sellers
Shop All
THINK KINK
Bondage bestsellers
BEST IN BED
Shop now
BOTTOM'S UP!
Heartfelt Coasters
CALEXOTICS
On sale now!
SIGN IN1-866-542-7283
Position Guide
Liberator Unzipped Blog
Factory Store
Account Settings Language Liberator LiberatorShop (PPC)
Home
Privacy Policy
Free Shipping on Orders Over $75
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is Protected.
When you make a purchase from Liberator, you provide us with personal information such as your name, address, phone number, credit card information, email address, and an order. We keep a record of this information which is covered by our privacy policy and is held in the strictest of confidence. All information submitted via our website is secure and private. From the time you visit our site until the package arrives at your door, and even afterwards, your entire transaction will be completed discretely and privately.
Your Information Is Only Used When Necessary
When you place an order with Liberator, we ask you to provide us with various types of information. These are used to verify credit card ownership and process your order. We do not sell your information to any third parties.
Your Name and Billing Address
This information is collected in order to verify that the person placing the order is the person who owns the credit card. This process is performed by an address verification system which uses the numeric value of your street address and your zip code. These two numbers are entered into the system and verified against the address where your credit card bill is sent. We do not send out marketing materials via postal mail, and you will never receive anything at this address unless it is also your shipping address where you would like to send your order.
Your Shipping Address
Your order will arrive at this address. It can be the same as your billing address.
Your Email Address
Your email address is used to send order-related emails such as order updates and confirmations, online shipping confirmations, and customer service inquiries. You also have the option to receive our Liberator Newsletter, or you may choose to opt-out.
Your Phone Number
We ship via UPS which requires a recipient contact number. You may be contacted by phone in case we need to reach you about your order in the event that there is a delay in manufacturing or shipping your order. Additionally, our customers do not always have access to email, and a phone number is used as an alternate method of communication. When it is necessary to contact our customers regarding their order, we try to provide email correspondence as often as possible. However, on occasion, phone contact is the easiest method. We will not solicit you or call for any reason other than in regards to your order.
Your Credit Card Information
We require your credit card number, expiration date, and security code in order to process your transaction. Your card is charged only after the order is shipped. We do not store any of your credit card information in our systems other than the last four digits of your credit card number and the expiration date. We do not keep your credit card numbers or security codes.
We Protect Your Privacy
At Liberator, we take great care in safeguarding your privacy by offering discrete packaging and billing. When you submit your information to us, it is encrypted and secure, and you will not receive any promotional materials from us if you do not wish to receive them.
Deleting Your Information
In compliance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), a customer may request at any time to obtain all stored information in our systems pertaining to them specifically. A customer may also request that all stored data pertaining to their name, address, email address, or credit card be deleted in our system. We are happy to oblige these requests. Please email our customer service department for any inquiries concerning this.
Discrete Packaging
We ship all of our packages in nondescript brown cardboard boxes that are sealed with reinforced tape. The return address on the label is listed as Fulfillment Center, and there is no indication of the contents of the package. Your privacy is our utmost concern. Please note all APO orders require Customs Documentation, which list the contents of the packages. This list will be visible on the outside of the boxes. The descriptions of the contents must be accurate to ensure deliverability. While the descriptions we use are generic, they will be visible.
Billing
All charges and authorizations on your credit card will appear as "OneUp Innovations".
Opt-Out
When you make a purchase with Liberator, you are required to provide your email address. This allows us to contact you with order updates and confirmations, online shipping confirmations, and customer service inquiries. Below the email address line in the order form you will notice the option to receive the Liberator Newsletter is automatically selected. The Liberator Newsletter provides you with information on sales, special offers, weekly promotional events, exclusive email discounts, and new products for sale. To opt-out of the Liberator Newsletter, simply uncheck the box. If you do elect to subscribe to our newsletter, please know that it is 100% US CAN-Spam compliant and you may unsubscribe or change your subscription preferences at any time.
Security
Liberator is secured with the industry standard SHA-256-bit SSL encryption. When you make a purchase with Liberator, you can be assured that your information is safe and secure. 18 U.S.C Section 2257 Compliance Notice - All Models are 18 years old or older. Liberator.com is operated by OneUp Innovations Inc., Atlanta, GA 30360, Copyright ©2020 U.S. Patent no. 6,925,669 Liberator is made here. It’s our pride and heritage to manufacture in America. Our 100+ employees thank you!
|
Site Map
|
Privacy Policy
